Kenneth, what drew you to the Tampa Bay
Buccaneers and free agency?
>> Uh, man, it was a great option for me
and um I wanted to be here last year,
but you know um I'm happy to be here
now, but it was a great opportunity for
me, you know, to be back in the South
where I'm from and um just come here.
Kim, what do you think last year did for
you just to just to see a bigger role
and a and a better production after four
years in Philadelphia? How much do you
think that helped kind of just elevate
you and and people's awareness of you
and all you could do?
>> Um I think it opened up a couple people
eyes to, you know, see what I really can
do and um you know, me going out there,
you know, um doing all I can on the
field basically just prove what I what I
basically really can do or what I really
been doing all my career and what have
been hidden, you know, and finally
coming to the light. Um, but you know,
I'm I'm very appreciative for, you know,
the opportunity that Pittsburgh have u
given me. Um, and for me to shine my
light and, you know, to come here and do
great things, too.
>> How much pride do you take in your forte
as a pass catcher, too?
>> I take very pride in it. Um, I work on
that a lot. You know, I work on what I
can do with my hands and and feet. And,
you know, I'm just taking a I'm just
very appreciative that the Lord gave me
these great hands to go out there and,
you know, do what I do. three. That's a
big number.
>> Yeah, that's a big number for, you know,
running back. Um, especially a running
back, too, to have those numbers. But,
um, you know, I took took pride in what
I do with catching the ball and, you
know, it worked out good for me.
>> What do you know about your your new
quarterback that's going to probably
help you with those numbers?
>> Yeah. Um, I know I know he's a very
tough guy. Um, I love exactly what he
does. Um um hopefully we can get a lot
of connection going and um him passing
the ball to the running back, us doing a
lot of things and um just going to be
excited to play football with him being
a side with him and um let's just take
over this division.
>> You come here with the new offensive
coordinator, Zack Robinson and uh what
do you know about his offense about him
and what kind of makes you excited to
play in it with your particular skill
set as a running back?
>> Um um I think he was in Atlanta last
year. Um just seeing the opportunity
that he gave to Bun and you know the
things that he have done with him
splitting him wide putting him in
different situation where he can go and
run routes. Um that's just that's that's
me all over again you know and um I'm
happy for that opportunity to go out
there and show what I can do in that
aspect and really just excited to you
know see what what he can do with all of
us in the running back room and what he
can do with the guys out wide and um
just grateful for that opportunity to be
with him. Kenneth, you made a a hell of
a catch against the Lions last year
against your new teammate Alex Enzelone.
>> What can you say about that particular
play and have you guys had a chance to
talk about that? I think went for a
touchdown.
>> Yeah, scored after that.
>> Yeah. Uh that was a that was a crazy
sequence. We was in a two-minute
situation and um we was driving the ball
down the field and uh Aaron had told me
to, you know, go out wide and run a
route. And I looked at him and said,
"What route?" He said, "Run a go." And I
was like, "Okay." I just went out ride
wide, ran the route, and you know, the
ball was in the air and I kind of like
looked back for it for a second. I
tripped over over Alex for a minute and
it like I just put my hand out to like
try to keep it from hitting the ground
and it just bounced right in my chest.
Had very good awareness to get up
knowing I wouldn't touch and get up and
go and score the ball. But it was a
great crazy sequence of things that
happened in that, you know, I drew a
pass interference. Um, got up and
scored. But it was it was a great
experience to, you know, go through
that. But I always tell all the kids
that I work out at my gym that, you
know, um, never give up on anything. You
know, that's just a great example of
never giving up on anything in your
life. You know,
>> Kathy, you know, Jaylen had a pretty
even split in terms of like snaps and
touches and all that last year. that
there's kind of a lot of two back
offenses in the NFL now and you seem to
have that kind of plays well with others
type uh quality. How important is that
and how do you see yourself fitting
together with Bucky here?
>> Um I think that was a great thing that
me and Jaylen did last year. Um they
they put us in great situations for us
to both succeed as a running back. Um he
had a thousand um rushing. I had a
thousand purpose. Um they both gave us a
great situation to you know go out and
be successful. Um that's just something
that we want to bring here, you know,
drive together with Bucky and knowing
that um Buckley is a is a selfless guy,
you know, understanding when I was
talking to him a couple times, you know,
just understand he's a selfless guy and
you know, we can feed off each other. We
can go out there and do things that's
very special and you know, you know, us
trusting one another and feeding feeding
off each other energy will, you know,
take us a long way.
>> You mentioned Rogers and he was really
complimentary of you. He's played with a
lot of good running backs. What What did
you learn just in a year you were able
to kind of play in that offense
together?
>> Um learning learning the small details,
you know, learning the small details
when you know you ask something, answer
it in the right way. Um like going out
being being very professional with what
you do. And um with him, man, it was
just it was just an honor to play with,
you know, a gold jacking type of guy
like that to like give me my respect and
see how hard I worked every day in
practice. And you know, he's he's one of
those guys that when he see somebody
that's good, he want to play with him.
And you know, he was very, very
appreciative of what I did. And um I
thank him for everything that he had
done for me, too. But man, man, it was
just amazing to play with him and a guy
that that really see true value in a
person.
>> When you look at the Steelers, you think
about the organization, you know, they
have Cam, TJ, you know, Aaron came last
year. You played alongside a thousand
yard runner. You were voted as the team
MVP.
>> What did that mean to you?
>> Um, that meant a lot, you know. Um, man,
I I just came to work every day and did
exactly what I needed to be doing. Um,
never caused any problems. I was always
about football, you know, and they seen
that value in me and the way I carried
myself throughout the building and um
the way I carried myself on the field, I
was all about business and wanted to win
and I had that winning mentality and it
just showed to them, you know. Um why
not choose this guy that loves football,
love to win, love to do great things and
come here to be our MVP, you know. But
man, I took that and I just ran with it
and um it just fueled me for the next
couple games I had for the end of the
season to go out and have 100 plus
allpurpose yards and you know that was
just me just wanting to be great for the
team.
>> I assume that you talked to both Jason
Light and Todd BS so far.
>> Yeah, I have.
>> What have they anything stand out of
what they told you? What they want from
you? What this team franchise is about?
>> Um no, not not exactly. It was all it
was all a welcome uh welcoming gift, you
know, just being happy that I'm here,
you know, and um when it come down, if
you're asking about roles, that haven't
been addressed yet, but you know,
football is football. When that time
comes, they'll be here. We'll get to
camp soon.
>> You might know something about your
special teams coach that came down here
before you.
>> Yeah, Danny. What do you say about
Danny?
>> Oh, man. I love Danny, man. I love the
way his his attitude towards the game.
um he comes ready to work. Soon as he
step out of his car, he's yelling about
something something good. But Danny is a
great guy, man. And I love playing
football for him. Um we going to get
this special team things turned around
real good. And you know, he brings that
energy each and every day.
>> What have you learned about the team's
culture here so far?
>> Um I'm I'm getting to that. You know,
I'm learning this culture as as much as
I can. This is really my first day here.
Um, but uh, I'm pretty sure from what I
seen from a distance is very high
intensity and what the guys do and I'm
just ready to fuel onto it. Add some
more fuel onto that fire.
>> You're going to miss those Pennsylvania
winters.
>> Yes, I will. And I'm happy I'm away from
right now. But hey, I will love this
heat too, you know. But at the same
time, that Pennsylvania cold, man, I'm
happy I'm from up there. And to your
point about culture, like from a
distance, you mentioned uh what what
kind of things could you pick up on from
a distance? I'm always curious to hear
what
>> what I mean on other teams think.
>> I mean, you can see the way Baker play
football, you know. I just see that, you
know, and like when you see something
like that, you you'll think it's
culturally, right? So, you just see
those type of things you want to add
onto that. So, that's that's that's the
type of things I see.
>> Hey, big question. When we write about
you, do you want us to call you Kenneth
or Kenny?
>> It can be Kenny, Kenneth, you know what
I'm saying? But whatever whatever you
write, you know what I'm saying? Just
long as it's good.
>> Do you have a preference though?
>> Uh, Kenny. Yeah.
>> Do you like to return kicks here like
you did last year? And do you enjoy
returning?
>> Um, I love returning kicks. You know,
whatever my my job will be, you know
what I'm saying? I'm going to embrace
that. Um, I love returning kicks. That
that that whole setup is fun. um got
good guys just blocking for you up
front. That whole setup is real nice and
I like it.
>> Ken, how would you describe yourself as
as a back or or maybe as a weapon?
>> Mhm.
>> How would you describe your
>> I describe myself as a as a uh whatever
I can do type of guy, you know, it's
it's a threat, you know, a real true
threat. And you know, teams really have
to
really teams really have to like, you
know, game plan real good to, you know,
go against a real threat like me. So,
um, I'm just going to call myself that
good threat.
>> Can can you talk about lining up at
receiver like you did a handful of times
and how you feel about that and how much
experience you had with that last year?
>> Um, I had a lot of experience with it.
Um, whenever I get an opportunity to
line up at receiver is know your job, do
your job. I go out there and do my job
the right way that is coached and I know
I just I just take that and just go with
it. um knowing footwork, knowing when to
get to depth or when I need to run this
route right on time or if I'm carrying
out a route for another guy to come
underneath or do anything like that, you
know, I know what I'm doing.
>> Anything else?
>> Welcome to
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> Thank you guys, man.